the SP
yeah
[Music]
yeah if you want to be successful in the
industry you can count on Microsoft
because Microsoft has a lot of talent
programs where where you can really get
your knowledge to build a career in BC
it's pretty much being able to implement
the best practices the problem is how do
you know the best practices and that is
where theoretical knowledge comes in but
also your practical knowledge uh as a
beginning consultant or a beginning
developer that's difficult you don't
have this practical knowledge just if
you can drive with experienced people
then you have the perfect combination if
you start in business Central you can
start as a consultant but you can
explore so many areas like sales Finance
or something else but if you think oh
this is nothing for me you can also
maybe start a job as project manager or
maybe start a more technical job and add
dig into the code you can do so many
things that makes it exciting and you
don't have to be know what you will be
doing the next 10 years now and for the
record for our developers in general we
can be nerdy in business Central